intelligrape.com 2014-07-01

# Privacy Policy

IntelliGrape Software Private Limied ("IntelliGrape" "we," or "us") knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by IntelliGrape when you access the IntelliGrape website, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources.

###### Information we collect

Our Service: We may collect personally identifiable information about you through our website when you register for an account, such as your email. We also collect data through our partners (customers) who use our Service (including by embedding our code on their websites) to analyze usage of their websites. When you visit such websites, your browser may send us certain information about you as described below. We do not send any promotional emails, however we may send you service related emails related to your account. 

Cookies Information: We may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets learn about your behavior and usage patterns when you are on our site. A cookie may also convey anonymous information about how you browse a partner website to us. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser's directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

Log File Information: Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page on our site. When you access the Service, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. 

Clear Gifs Information: When you access the Service or are on our web site, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your IntelliGrape account is collected using these clear gifs. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our Service, and make IntelliGrape better for our users and partners. These technologies mentioned above do not collect personal information about you and only collect data in the aggregate. 

How We Use Your Information: We use the information that we collect to operate and maintain our Service. We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) monitor the effectiveness of our Service (b) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (c) diagnose or fix technology problems.

###### How We Share Your Information

Personally Identifiable Information: IntelliGrape will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of IntelliGrape (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers). As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain IntelliGrape services and those of our partners. Non-personally identifiable information may be stored indefinitely. 

How We Protect Your Information: IntelliGrape is concerned with protecting your privacy and data, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to IntelliGrape or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our industry standard physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

Compromise of Personal Information: In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, IntelliGrape will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law. 

Your Choices About Your Information: You can review and correct the information about you that IntelliGrape keeps on file by logging into your account to update your password and billing information. Alternately, you can contact us directly at [info@intelligrape.com](). 

Children's Privacy: Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, IntelliGrape does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to IntelliGrape. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [info@intelligrape.com](). 

Notification Procedures: It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Service, as determined by IntelliGrape in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

Features on our site: If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums. We also have testimonials on our site, for which users have given permission to have their personal information posted on our site with their testimonial. 

Links to Other Web Sites: Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of other sites. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

Changes to Our Privacy Policy: If we change our privacy policies and procedures materially, we will post those changes on the Service to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at info@intelligrape.com, or send mail to:  
IntelliGrape Software Private Limited  
L-6, NSEZ, NOIDA – 201305
